whitefence.com 2016-10-18

# Privacy Policy | Allconnect

Allconnect seeks to safeguard your privacy whether you are just browsing our website at <http://www.allconnect.com/corporate/privacy.html> or Allconnect.com (the "website" ) or selecting products and services through our website (the "Services"). We are committed to protecting your information and this privacy policy outlines the limited manner in which we will use your information to provide you Services. By using our website or using our Services, you consent to let us gather and use your information as set forth in our policy then in effect at the time of our use of your information.

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, [www.allconnect.com](https://www.allconnect.com/). In order to view our relationship with TRUSTe please visit the validation page visible by clicking on the TRUSTe seal. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at [https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request)

  * What Are The Important Terms Used Throughout This Privacy Policy?
  * What Types Of Information Do We Collect, How Do We Use it and To Whom Do We Disclose It?
  * What Information May Be Collected By Third Parties?
  * Website Tracking
  * What Are Cookies and How Do We Use Them?
  * What Are Your Choices in How We Use Your Information?
  * How Do We Protect Your Information?
  * Data Retention
  * How Do You Safeguard Your Passwords?
  * What If You Lose Your Password or It Becomes Compromised?
  * Can Children Use the website?
  * Short Message Service (SMS)
  * How Will You Know of Changes to this Privacy Policy?

**What Are The Important Terms Used Throughout This Privacy Policy?**

Throughout this privacy policy we use several specialized terms. "Personally Identifiable Information" is information that tells us specifically who you are, like your name, street address, birth date, email address, billing address, user ID number (including, if applicable, customer ID number and account number), social security number, credit card number, and other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing. "User Information" means all Personally Identifiable Information and any other forms of information discussed in this privacy policy, including the Internet Protocol (IP) address of a user's computer. We use the term "aggregate" when we combine information from various persons or users. Information is said to be "anonymized" if it does not identify individual persons or entities or associate a particular person or entity with such information.

**What Types Of Information Do We Collect, How Do We Use it and To Whom Do We Disclose It?**

Visiting Our Site. When you visit our website to browse, we may collect and store the domain name and host from which you access the Internet (e.g., google.com), the IP address of your computer, your browser software and operating system and your entity identification. We may use this information to organize and analyze IP addresses so that we can provide items such as efficient service, enhance security, monitor appropriate usage and produce traffic volume statistics. This type of non-Personally Identifiable information may be shared with third parties, such as when we aggregate and disclose site traffic information for marketing and commercial purposes. When you visit our website, you may also choose certain options such as (i) Your Account, (ii) About Allconnect, (iii) Bundles, Phone, TV, Internet, Utilities and Home Service, (iv) Customer Service and (v) Contact Us to obtain more information about us, our business associates and our Services. Through these options, you may provide us with Personally Identifiable Information. We will collect, use and disclose such Personally Identifiable Information as further described below in Using Our Services.

Using Our Services. When you use our Services, you must through our initial checkout process or subsequent order placements provide Personally Identifiable Information, including your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and billing information for you to properly and fully receive the offered Services. We collect and store this Personally Identifiable Information and any modifications that either we or you make to that information. Except as set forth in this policy, we will not reveal any such Personally Identifiable Information to any third party without the consent of the provider of such information, except that we may share User Information with our business associates who assist us in administering the Services. In such cases, the business associates are permitted to use this information only in order to carry out the services Allconnect has contracted for. Furthermore, we may use, disclose or transfer certain User Information (i) to provide you the Services or information you request; (ii) to send you additional information about your ordered services such as a confirmation, reminder, problem status or change order; (iii) to send you a newsletter or other marketing materials; (iv) to protect the confidentiality or security of your records; (v) to comply with government requests if appropriate for your protection or in connection with an investigation or prosecution, court order, or subpoena or similar legal process; (vi) in connection with a sale or merger of Allconnect or other change in corporate control (and you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your Personally Identifiable Information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your Personally Identifiable Information), or (vii) for other legally permissible purposes. We may also share aggregate anonymized data relating to the transactions on the site and use of the Services for marketing, research and other purposes.

From time to time, we may send you survey forms or include survey forms on our site asking you for information regarding your use of our Services. For the most part, we will only disclose your survey responses that contain anonymized data to our business associates who assist us in administering the Services. However, we may share email addresses with business associates who assist us in administering the Services.

**Blog / Forum**

Our website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your Personally Identifiable Information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [customercare@allconnect.com](mailto:customercare@allconnect.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your Personally Identifiable Information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Surveys**

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain Personally Identifiable Information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

We use this information to send surveys; and we may use this information notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic or personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), and to send participants an email newsletter. We use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company is prohibited from using our users’ Personally Identifiable Information for any other purpose. 

**What Information May Be Collected By Third Parties?**

When accessing our website or Services, you may have the option to obtain a coupon or purchase products and services from a third party through our website. For example, when you sign up to initiate service to your home by a utility or other service provider under Your Account, Allconnect passes the Personally Identifiable Information needed for that service on to the third party utility or service provider that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your Personally Identifiable Information only as necessary to provide these services to us. Please pay close attention when you obtain a coupon or are purchasing products and services from a third party because different rules may apply to those parties' use or disclosure of such information regardless of their affiliation or relationship with us. This privacy policy only addresses the use and disclosure of User Information collected by us and not third parties from whom you may obtain a coupon or purchase products and services.

Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These Features may collect your Internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.

Finally, our website may provide links to third party websites. If you enter a third party website, the owners of that website may use and disclose your information in accordance with their own privacy policy, and you may begin receiving emails from such third party. We have no responsibility or liability for the independent actions or policies of these independent sites, and are not responsible for the content, terms or privacy practices of such sites. In order to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, you may wish to first review the privacy policies of any third party from whom you obtain coupons, products or services on our website, or before providing any information on a third party website.

**Website Tracking**

We may employ third party analytics partners to help us provide a better user experience by continually learning and adjusting to what our visitors find useful. Unique identifiers (such as web beacons or tags) are used to track the online movements of Web users. This allows us to see which pages are most visited on our site, so we can continue to provide useful content to our visitors. The collected information is used to learn more about which aspects of our site customers find useful and effective.

**What Are Cookies and How Do We Use Them?**

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication, and as further described below. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

**Tracking Technologies**

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Allconnect and our partners e.g. marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

**Analytics / Log Files**

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

**Behavioral Targeting**

We partner with third parties to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies and/or tags to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by visiting [www.allconnect.com/corporate/enable-and-disable-cookies.html](http://www.allconnect.com/corporate/enable-and-disable-cookies.html). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

**Google AdSense/Adwords**

We may use Google AdSense to publish ads on this site. When you view or click on an ad a cookie will be set to help better provide advertisements that may be of interest to you on this and other Web sites.

**Local Storage**

We use Local Storage (LSs) such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity may use LSOs such as HTML 5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. To manage Flash cookies, please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

**What Are Your Choices in How We Use Your Information?**

If you use our Services, then you have voluntarily consented to the collection and use of your Personally Identifiable Information as described in this privacy policy and other written documentation provided to you regarding the Services. If you do not want us to use your information as described herein, please contact us at [customercare@allconnect.com](mailto:customercare@allconnect.com). At the time of initiating Your Account, you will be given a choice whether to receive promotional emails from Allconnect. Each promotional email you receive from us will provide you a specific opt-out mechanism to allow you to unsubscribe from receipt of these promotional emails. However, without the use of your information, we may not be able to provide you the Services or the same quality of Services you request. By accessing your profile under Your Account at <https://www.allconnect.com/login> on our website, you may also update, delete or remove Personally Identifiable Information from our database or change your marketing preferences, or you may do this by contacting us at [customercare@allconnect.com](mailto:customercare@allconnect.com), or at the following address:

Allconnect, Inc.  
980 Hammond Drive, #1000  
Atlanta, Georgia 30328  
Attention: Privacy

We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

If you remove certain information from your account, then we will only retain copies of such information as are necessary for us to comply with governmental orders, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, enforce any agreement you have entered into with us and as otherwise reasonably necessary.

Allconnect does not sell, rent or disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for such parties' marketing purposes. However, as noted above under What Information May Be Collected by Third Parties, where you agree to obtain products, services or coupons from third parties through our website, you may receive marketing communications from such third parties.

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**

We employ and maintain technology and security measures designed to protect User Information. When you submit sensitive information via our site, that information is subject to a variety of protections both on-line and off-line, including password-protected systems, firewalls and transport layer (TLS) encryption technology. On a periodic basis, we also perform security audits of our data center to help ensure a more secure site. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed as 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your User Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or receive from us. If you have any questions about the security of your Personally Identifiable Information, you can contact us at [customercare@allconnect.com](mailto:customercare@allconnect.com).

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [customercare@allconnect.com](mailto:customercare@allconnect.com). WWe will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**How Do You Safeguard Your Passwords?**

When you initially register for our Services, you will choose a member ID and a password. To subsequently sign-in as a member, you will need to enter your correct member ID and password. We designed this password-protected system to help safeguard your User Information. To help us further protect your User Information, we ask that you not, lend, give, or otherwise disclose any member ID or passwords to any unauthorized person, or permit any unauthorized person to use your accounts or related member ID or passwords except as specifically permitted by this privacy policy or other instructions regarding the Services. Moreover, we will never ask for your member ID or password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email.

**What If You Lose Your Password or It Becomes Compromised?**

If your member ID or password has been compromised for any reason, then you should immediately notify us so that we may issue you a new member ID or password. Any loss of control of your member ID or password may result in the loss of control over Personally Identifiable Information. If you fail to protect your member ID or password, then you will be responsible for any actions taken on your behalf or by any person using your member ID or password.

**Can Children Use the website?**

The website is intended for use by adults, and we ask that children under the age of 18 do not use the website and do not submit any Personally Identifiable Information to us.

**Short Message Service (“SMS”)**

We may make available a service through which you can receive messages on your wireless device via short message service (“SMS Service”). We may collect your mobile phone number through a text message you send to us or as you may provide to us on our website; when you provide us with your mobile phone number, you expressly agree to receive SMS Service messages (including SMS and MMS) to that phone number.

We may send you SMS messages with promotional offers, product and service information, and transactional alerts. Examples of activities that would generate a transactional alert include your making an online transaction and when an order you have placed has been processed. Sometimes our SMS may advise you to visit our website www.allconnect.com for details or our other co-branded or partner websites. You agree and consent to be contacted by us through the use of email, and/or telephone calls and/or SMS text messages to your cellular, home or work phone numbers, as well as any other phone number you have provided in conjunction with Your Account.

Your wireless carrier’s standard rates apply to these messages, and you may change your mind at any time by following the instructions on this website or in the message you receive. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device you use to sign up for the SMS Service, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges. To use the SMS Service, you must be 18 years of age or older and reside in the United States. You must first register and provide all required Personally Identifiable Information, which may include, for example, your name, SMS address, wireless carrier and, if fees are applicable to the SMS Service you subscribe to, billing information (either your credit card information or mobile service carrier information if applicable fees will be billed through your carrier). We may also obtain the date, time and content of your messages in the course of your use of the SMS Service. We will use the information we obtain in connection with our SMS Service in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If fees are charged to your wireless account invoice, we may provide your carrier with your applicable information in connection therewith. Your wireless carrier and other service providers may also collect data about your wireless device usage, and their practices are governed by their own policies.

You acknowledge and agree that the SMS Service is provided via wireless systems which use radios (and other means) to transmit communications over complex networks. We do not guarantee that your use of the SMS Service will be private or secure, and we are not liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience. You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the SMS Service. We may also access the content of your account and/or wireless account with your carrier for the purpose of identifying and resolving technical problems and/or service-related complaints.

THE SMS SERVICE IS PROVIDED "AS IS, WHERE IS." TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, ALLCONNECT HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS, IMPLIED, OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.

**How Will You Know of Changes to this Privacy Policy?**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, the practices of this site or your dealings with this site, please contact us using the information below:

Allconnect, Inc.  
980 Hammond Drive, NE #1000  
Atlanta, Georgia 30328

Effective Date: 10/06/2015

Copyright © 2015 Allconnect, Inc.
